<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dan Quan</title>
    <link>https://quan.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dan Quan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 15:38:10 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://quan.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Books Read in 2019</title>
      <link>https://quan.io/blog/books-read-in-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 11:44:23 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quan.io/blog/books-read-in-2019/</guid>
      <description>62 books in total.
 Lord of Chaos: Book Six of The Wheel of Time The Fires of Heaven: Book Five of The Wheel of Time Catch and Kill: Lies, Spies, and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators The Shadow Rising: Book Four of The Wheel of Time The Dragon Reborn: Book Three of The Wheel of Time The Golden Compass: His Dark Materials, Book 1 Blowout: Corrupted Democracy, Rogue State Russia, and the Richest, Most Destructive Industry on Earth The Great Hunt: Book Two of The Wheel Of Time Ultralearning: Master Hard Skills, Outsmart the Competition, and Accelerate Your Career Thinking in Bets: Making Smarter Decisions When You Don&amp;rsquo;t Have All the Facts The Eye of the World: Book One of The Wheel of Time The Heart of the Buddha&amp;rsquo;s Teaching: Transforming Suffering into Peace, Joy, and Liberation Making Space, Clutter Free: The Last Book on Decluttering You&amp;rsquo;ll Ever Need Talking to Strangers: What We Should Know About the People We Don&amp;rsquo;t Know The Obelisk Gate: The Broken Earth, Book 2 The Stone Sky Set for Life: Dominate Life, Money, and the American Dream The Fifth Season: The Broken Earth, Book 1 The Ocean at the End of the Lane: A Novel Why Buddhism Is True: The Science and Philosophy of Meditation and Enlightenment Arcanum Unbounded: The Cosmere Collection Warbreaker Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind Elantris The Bands of Mourning Shadows of Self The Alloy of Law: A Mistborn Novel Moneyball: The Art of Winning an Unfair Game The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck: A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life The Well of Ascension: Mistborn, Book 2 The Hero of Ages: Mistborn, Book 3 No-Nonsense Buddhism for Beginners: Clear Answers to Burning Questions About Core Buddhist Teachings Essentialism: The Disciplined Pursuit of Less 10% Happier: How I Tamed the Voice in My Head, Reduced Stress Without Losing My Edge, and Found a Self-Help That Actually Works The Bullet Journal Method: Track the Past, Order the Present, Design the Future The Final Empire: Mistborn Book 1 Principles: Life and Work Good Omens Factfulness: Ten Reasons We&amp;rsquo;re Wrong About the World - and Why Things Are Better Than You Think Mindset: The New Psychology of Success The Graveyard Book Atomic Habits: An Easy &amp;amp; Proven Way to Build Good Habits &amp;amp; Break Bad Ones Work Optional: Retire Early the Non-Penny-Pinching Way The Art of Racing in the Rain So Here&amp;rsquo;s the Thing&amp;hellip;: Notes on Growing Up, Getting Older, and Trusting Your Gut Playing with FIRE (Financial Independence Retire Early): How Far Would You Go for Financial Freedom?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Phoenix to Kubernetes from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://quan.io/blog/deploying-phoenix-to-kubernetes-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 18:43:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quan.io/blog/deploying-phoenix-to-kubernetes-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kubernetes is such an exciting technology, but it can be overwhelming when starting. There are many reasons to use Kubernetes, and likely an equal number of valid reasons to use something different. I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything interesting or new to add to that debate though. I use Kubernetes at work and for personal projects, and I love the options it gives me for deploying applications. There&amp;rsquo;s an initial burden when getting the cluster set up and learning the basics, but deploying applications is easy and quick after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Erlang&#39;s Observer in Kubernetes for an Elixir Release</title>
      <link>https://quan.io/blog/using-erlangs-observer-in-kubernetes-for-an-elixir-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 15:25:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quan.io/blog/using-erlangs-observer-in-kubernetes-for-an-elixir-release/</guid>
      <description>Erlang&amp;rsquo;s observer is awesome. There are a lot of anecdotes on the usefulness of it for debugging production systems, and one of my favorites is how the Phoenix team used it to find a process that was filling up it&amp;rsquo;s mailbox.
Most of the guides out there are for using it with vanilla ssh.
We&amp;rsquo;ll work through getting a local Observer talking with a Kubernetes pod in production.
Pre-requisites  A Phoenix App using Elixir 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://quan.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 15:38:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quan.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Experience I&amp;rsquo;ve been a software developer at Braintree Payments since 2014 working primarily in Ruby and Java.
For more of my portfolio, check out my github.
Conference Talks Pairing and Policing - A talk given at Rocky Mountain Ruby about how my experiences as a cop prepared me for being good at pair programming.
Side Projects budget.sh - This is my current, work in progress side project. It&amp;rsquo;s an open source budgeting application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://quan.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 15:18:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quan.io/home/</guid>
      <description>Software Engineer
San Diego, CA</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>